https://www.ucov.com/redesign/privacy-policies

ABOUT USServicesService TimesWhat to ExpectDirections / How To Find UsOur Vision and BeliefsOur StoryWhat is this "gospel?"Staff and LeadersMinistry Directors and StaffElder TeamJob OpportunitiesContact UsSERMONSWatch SermonsListen to SermonsStudy QuestionsSermon ResourcesMINISTRIESChildren & YouthBirth thru 6th GradeKidZone OnlineBreakaway 2020Baptism for 1st-6th KidsFrontier Ranch Jr Camp5th/6th GradeGlacier EventsGod's Design for SexJr HighEdge EventsEdge Campership ApplicationEdge Campership DonationEdge StaffApply for Edge StaffSr HighSummit EventsConfirmation 2020/21CampershipSummit StaffSummit: Apply for Summit StaffCrisis HelpCollegeInclusionWeekday PreSchoolUCNSWho We AreOur Story - About UCNSCurriculum OverviewMeet Our Staff TeamDriving DirectionsUCNS BoardSchool YearSchool Reopening InformationRegistrationDaily ScheduleCalendarTuition & FeesEnrollment InformationUCNS Upcoming EventsMore InfoFAQsUCNS Photo TourUCNS DonationsFundraisingFormsEmploymentParent TestimonialsAdultsJust for WomenWomen's MinistryWomen's EventsMothers of PreSchoolers (MOPS)Just for MenYoung Adult/CareerSeasoned AdultsAdult EdMembershipCARESubmit a Prayer RequestUCC Prayer RoomImmediate CareCounseling CenterCelebrate RecoveryENGAGEServeLocal OutreachGlobal OutreachServe at UCCSkills SurveyWorship TeamKidZone VolunteerLife Groups / Small GroupsTake a ClassAdult ClassesThe Meaning of MembershipWhat is Baptism?SubscribeConnection CardANNOUNCEMENTSNews & AnnouncementsPublicity Request FormLobby Table RequestGIVEGiving OnlineGiving FAQsWhat Are These Funds?
Privacy Policies
ABOUT USServicesService TimesWhat to ExpectDirections / How To Find UsOur Vision and BeliefsOur StoryWhat is this "gospel?"Staff and LeadersMinistry Directors and StaffElder TeamJob OpportunitiesContact UsSERMONSWatch SermonsListen to SermonsStudy QuestionsSermon ResourcesMINISTRIESChildren & YouthBirth thru 6th GradeKidZone OnlineBreakaway 2020Baptism for 1st-6th KidsFrontier Ranch Jr Camp5th/6th GradeGlacier EventsGod's Design for SexJr HighEdge EventsEdge Campership ApplicationEdge Campership DonationEdge StaffApply for Edge StaffSr HighSummit EventsConfirmation 2020/21CampershipSummit StaffSummit: Apply for Summit StaffCrisis HelpCollegeInclusionWeekday PreSchoolUCNSWho We AreOur Story - About UCNSCurriculum OverviewMeet Our Staff TeamDriving DirectionsUCNS BoardSchool YearSchool Reopening InformationRegistrationDaily ScheduleCalendarTuition & FeesEnrollment InformationUCNS Upcoming EventsMore InfoFAQsUCNS Photo TourUCNS DonationsFundraisingFormsEmploymentParent TestimonialsAdultsJust for WomenWomen's MinistryWomen's EventsMothers of PreSchoolers (MOPS)Just for MenYoung Adult/CareerSeasoned AdultsAdult EdMembershipCARESubmit a Prayer RequestUCC Prayer RoomImmediate CareCounseling CenterCelebrate RecoveryENGAGEServeLocal OutreachGlobal OutreachServe at UCCSkills SurveyWorship TeamKidZone VolunteerLife Groups / Small GroupsTake a ClassAdult ClassesThe Meaning of MembershipWhat is Baptism?SubscribeConnection CardANNOUNCEMENTSNews & AnnouncementsPublicity Request FormLobby Table RequestGIVEGiving OnlineGiving FAQsWhat Are These Funds?
Privacy Policies
Privacy Policies
Photo Policy
All photos used on this website, brochures, or other documentation are the property of University Covenant Church (UCC) unless otherwise noted. Including the images of our church family on our website or brochures can be a great way to motivate and encourage individuals to become more involved. It is also a helpful tool for guests who may be curious about what our events and activities are like. It is for these reasons that we feature personal photographs on UCC’s ucov.com website, brochures, and other documentation. However, we realize the importance of maintaining the privacy of the individual(s) pictured on this website, our brochures, or other documentation. To this end, UCC ensures:
The last name of a pictured individual is never published alongside a photograph (except for staff and leadership pages) on our web pages
Anyone listed as a contact will be an adult
No identifying information will be posted on the internet (see our privacy policy)
In the case of a group photo, first names may be mentioned, but we will not disclose which individuals are standing where in said photo (except for staff and leadership pages)
UCC reserves the right to amend this policy at any time.
Questions or concerns regarding this policy should be addressed to the site webservant or site maintainer.
Privacy Policy
University Covenant Church (UCC) respects your right to privacy and understands your desire to protect personally identifiable information. When you are visiting this website, we collect statistical information concerning where you go on the site, what browser you use, operating system and IP address. This information aids us in the future development of our site in order to meet the various needs of our guests. By using this website, you are giving us your express consent to use the information that we collect about you in the manner described in this policy.
Please be aware, the off-site links UCC provides have no direct affiliation with this website. These sites are not bound by our privacy policy. If you have concerns about any of these third-party sites, please read their privacy policy and/or contact the site administrator.
The personally identifiable information we collect is done so by the consent of the individual volunteering said information. (Personally identifiable information is any information that could be used to identify you personally.)
Information submitted to us is only available to UCC staff and volunteers and is used only for UCC ministry purposes. For some ministry purposes UCC may communicate to you through a contracted third party service provider. We screen these service providers to ensure that they do not share, sell, or rent individual personal information that we provide to them. UCC will not sell or rent your personal information to third parties.
If you received a mailing from us, (a) your email address is either listed with us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving University Covenant Church information in the future (”opt-in”), or (b) UCC has this information as a result of your individual or family relationship with us.
Each email sent contains an easy, automated way for you to cease receiving email from us, or to change your expressed interests. If you wish to do this, simply follow the instructions at the end of any email.
If you have received unwanted, unsolicited email sent via this system or purporting to be sent via this system, please forward a copy of that email with your comments to the ucov.com webservant for review.
University Covenant Church reserves the right to amend this policy at any time.
315 Mace Blvd,
Davis,
CA
95618
Email Us
Contact Us
530.756.3923
FaithConnector Church Websites
ABOUT USServicesService TimesWhat to ExpectDirections / How To Find UsOur Vision and BeliefsOur StoryWhat is this "gospel?"Staff and LeadersMinistry Directors and StaffElder TeamJob OpportunitiesContact UsSERMONSWatch SermonsListen to SermonsStudy QuestionsSermon ResourcesMINISTRIESChildren & YouthBirth thru 6th GradeKidZone OnlineBreakaway 2020Baptism for 1st-6th KidsFrontier Ranch Jr Camp5th/6th GradeGlacier EventsGod's Design for SexJr HighEdge EventsEdge Campership ApplicationEdge Campership DonationEdge StaffApply for Edge StaffSr HighSummit EventsConfirmation 2020/21CampershipSummit StaffSummit: Apply for Summit StaffCrisis HelpCollegeInclusionWeekday PreSchoolUCNSWho We AreOur Story - About UCNSCurriculum OverviewMeet Our Staff TeamDriving DirectionsUCNS BoardSchool YearSchool Reopening InformationRegistrationDaily ScheduleCalendarTuition & FeesEnrollment InformationUCNS Upcoming EventsMore InfoFAQsUCNS Photo TourUCNS DonationsFundraisingFormsEmploymentParent TestimonialsAdultsJust for WomenWomen's MinistryWomen's EventsMothers of PreSchoolers (MOPS)Just for MenYoung Adult/CareerSeasoned AdultsAdult EdMembershipCARESubmit a Prayer RequestUCC Prayer RoomImmediate CareCounseling CenterCelebrate RecoveryENGAGEServeLocal OutreachGlobal OutreachServe at UCCSkills SurveyWorship TeamKidZone VolunteerLife Groups / Small GroupsTake a ClassAdult ClassesThe Meaning of MembershipWhat is Baptism?SubscribeConnection CardANNOUNCEMENTSNews & AnnouncementsPublicity Request FormLobby Table RequestGIVEGiving OnlineGiving FAQsWhat Are These Funds?
Search
